**Add2it.com Marketing Pty Ltd: InfinityTrafficBoost (ACN 132 904 315) as trustee for Add2it.com Marketing Trust (ABN 70 591 880 591) provides software scripts & services for your online business success.  
InfinityTrafficBoost.com is owned by Add2it.com Marketing Pty Ltd as trustee for Add2it.com Marketing Trust.**

**Commitment to protect your privacy**

In your relationship with Add2it.com Marketing Pty Ltd, you share personal information with us. Such information may include your name, address, telephone numbers and email address, tax file number, bank account details, date of birth and other personal details in connection with transactions entered into by you with us. We understand how important it is to protect your personal information. This document sets out our privacy policy commitment in respect of personal information you provide to us. Further privacy information may apply depending on the business in Add2it.com Marketing Pty Ltd with which you deal with. If additional terms and conditions apply to you, they will appear on that business’ website. We encourage you to visit our websites regularly for any updates to our privacy policies.

**Collection, maintenance and disclosure of personal information**

A member of Add2it.com Marketing Pty Ltd will collect and hold your personal information for the purpose of:

* assisting it to provide you with the relevant product and/or service;
* letting you know about other products and/or services which might interest you; or
* assisting us generally in managing your transactions with us.

The personal information we request is optional, but we may not be able to fulfil your request or provide you with our products and services without it. Where reasonably practical, we will collect your personal information only directly from you. For example, if you order a sample or brochure, a member of Add2it.com Marketing Pty Ltd may ask you to provide us with your name, address and contact details in order for us to fulfil the request. We may, however, also collect personal information from other parties such as other members of Add2it.com Marketing Pty Ltd (except where you tell us not to), credit reporting agencies, unrelated third parties (such as our share registry) as well as from your representative (such as your legal or financial adviser) and publicly available sources of information.

**What do we do with the information we collect?**

We may keep and file all personal information you provide when dealing with us to assist us in providing you with our services and information of interest in respect of your business. For example, a member of Add2it.com Marketing Pty Ltd may send publications or other market information on our products and services to you or follow up on your interest in particular products and services. Add2it.com Marketing Pty Ltd discloses your personal information to those employees or advisers who need to know that information to assist us in providing you with our range of products and services. We may also disclose information to affiliates and other third parties necessary to process your transactions or service your account (including our share registry, print service providers, call centres and mail houses, our accountants, auditors and lawyers and credit reporting agencies). We may also disclose your personal information in corporate transactions involving the transfer of all or part of the assets or business of a member of Add2it.com Marketing Pty Ltd or in a corporate restructure. If we do this, we generally require these parties to protect your information in the same way we do. We may also be required or authorised by law to disclose your personal information. For example, we may disclose your personal information to a court in response to a subpoena or to the Australian Taxation Office. We will also disclose information to other persons where you have provided your consent to do so.

**What rights do you have in relation to personal information which we collect and hold?**

Add2it.com Marketing Pty Ltd takes all reasonable steps to ensure that the personal information we collect, use and disclose is accurate, complete and up-to-date. If you become aware of any errors in your personal information or you change your personal details such as your name, address or bank account details, we ask you to contact us as soon as possible so that we may update our records. You can contact our Privacy Officer if you would like details of your personal information which we may hold about you or if you would like us to correct it. We will disclose to you such information, subject to certain exceptions allowed by law. We may require you to complete a request form before disclosing information. We also reserve the right to charge a fee. You may also contact our Privacy Officer to request us to stop using your personal information to contact you about our products and services. If you no longer conduct business with us, you can ask us to remove your personal information we hold about you. Subject to our legal obligations and responsibilities, we will take reasonable steps to destroy or de-identify your personal information.

**Protecting your personal information**

Add2it.com Marketing Pty Ltd takes all reasonable steps to protect your personal information from misuse and loss and unauthorised access and disclosure. These steps include access control for our buildings, confidentiality obligations imposed on our employees and use of security measures for system access.

**Your privacy on the Internet**

**Our websites**

This privacy policy applies to the various websites operated by Add2it.com Marketing Pty Ltd under various domain names. Add2it.com Marketing Pty Ltd operates websites which may utilise ‘cookies’ to collect personal information. If you transact electronically with a member of Add2it.com Marketing Pty Ltd you should refer to the website of that member for more information on its website privacy and security procedures.

**Information collected from this website**

When you visit a website of Add2it.com Marketing Pty Ltd, we may collect the following information from you: domain name, your name, information you volunteer such as email addresses. We may also collect statistical data, such as the date and times of visits as well as the number and pages viewed by each visitor, which is utilised to evaluate the performance and usefulness of our website.

**Email Usage**

While we take care that the personal information you give us on our websites is protected, the Internet is not a secure environment. If you send us information, including your email address, it is sent at your own risk. Our websites do not capture email addresses without your permission. If, however, you provide your email address to us, it may be used by Add2it.com Marketing Pty Ltd to send you information relating to our and related products and services. If we send you an email which you do not wish to receive in the future, please use the unsubscribe link or follow the unsubscribe instructions at the bottom of that email or [notify us](https://reply2frank.com/) and your email address will be removed from our system.

**Private Information Security**

Add2it.com Marketing Pty Ltd takes all reasonable security measures to protect personal information from loss, unauthorised access, destruction, misuse, modification or disclosure. For your safety and protection, your credit card information is not stored on our servers.  Our payment gateway provider, Payeer, keep this information encrypted and secure on your behalf. We do not, however, accept any responsibility for the unauthorised access of personal information held by Add2it.com Marketing Pty Ltd. You may be able to access external websites by clicking on links we have provided. Those other websites are not subject to the privacy standards of Add2it.com Marketing Pty Ltd and we are not responsible for their privacy practices or the content of such other websites. You should contact those websites directly to ascertain their privacy standards, policies and procedures.

**3rd Party Disclosure**

Customer email addresses, street address, city, zip code, messaging ID's and ABN / GST information, whether public or private, will not be sold, exchanged, transferred, or given to any other company for any reason whatsoever, without the consent of the customer, other than for the express purpose of delivering the purchased product or service requested by the customer.

**Who do you contact?**

Our Privacy Officer can be contacted at:

**Add2it.com Marketing Pty Ltd: InfinityTrafficBoost**  
Frank Bauer, Dept. ITB  
P.O. Box 290  
Stanhope Gardens NSW 2768  
Australia  
Phone: +61-2-8005-8475  
Support: [https://Reply2Frank.com](https://reply2frank.com/)

**Changes to this privacy statement**

This privacy statement has been adopted by Add2it.com Marketing Pty Ltd to be consistent with the National Privacy Principles (NPPs) as set out in the Privacy Act 1988 (Cth). The NPPs can be found at [www.privacy.gov.au](http://www.privacy.gov.au/). We may change our privacy policies from time to time to comply with new laws or industry codes of practice which are developed. It is your responsibility to refer to our privacy policies from time to time to familiarise yourself with any changes.
